Good morning Ashish, there are many news today. We will
start with insurance companies
where companies have announced Make A Data.
In the general insurance business, we have seen
about 18% annual growth in premiums.
In the health insurance business, we are seeing about 23% growth.
This is their average. Now let's come to what the company has
delivered. ICC
Lombard's map is
showing premium growth of 21%. However, there is some dampness in the air-on-air market share. There is a
decline of 10 basis points. New India
Shares is seeing a 10% increase in premiums.
Its market share is
travelling more. There is a decline of about 144 basis
points.
And if you talk about Star Health, there is
definitely a 16% increase in Make A Premium here. And the market share was
seen increasing by about three basis points very recently. So, insurance stocks will be in the
red first. Yesterday we were telling you that
today is a big day for Maruti. Jeevan will be seen launching.
Pricing will be monitored, so
that stock is anyway on the radar.
Toilet Power: You should keep this in mind because
they have
signed a Memorandum of Understanding with the Maharashtra government,
where it has been announced to set up three pump storage
hydro projects. The
projects will actually be of 5700 MW capacity at three sites
in Karjat, Maval, and Junnar. These projects will be
coming up, and the investment will be Rs
27,000 crore. This symbolic
project is a sizable project,
which Talent Power has actually been the undertaker for the
Maharashtra government.
Deepak Fertilizers will actually be implemented in the next five years. Each
unit of this will be kept at Rs 900 crore.
Today, two big government companies will remain at home.
One is Hindustan Aeronautics,
because according to information sources,
news came out yesterday evening that it has received in-
principle approval. And
regarding the recent deal, where the administration has
given permission that it will be seen
producing jet engines in India in collaboration with Health.
And the recent deal is a very old
car, and under that, this is actually an update.  If engines are
seen being produced, then this is in
fact a big opportunity for the hall.
For this, they had set up a separate unit in Orissa, so it will be seen
decreasing there. A
big update has come for engineers. Engineer India has
won a contract worth around Rs 505 crore
from Nalco and then a contract worth Rs 15-50 crore
from Jindal Steel. So,
together, contracts worth Rs 2000 crore are
seen coming their way. A company had
shared the details yesterday, so these are some of the stocks.